virtualassistantjobs.com 2013-08-11

# VOT: Virtual Office Temps Administrative Services & Virtual Assistants: Work At Home Positions Are Available!

| 

Virtual Office Temps, Virtual Assistant Jobs 

ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS   
Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing http://www.longerdays.com, you acknowledge and fully understand Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Job's Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES   
Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

THIS SITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER SITES   
Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other websites to which the Site links or to which link to the Site. By clicking on a link, logo or other item, or using certain services available on the   
Site, including the online communication services, please note that you may no longer be on the Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs. To check what Internet location you are on, note the URL at the top and/or bottom of your browser. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of that website whenever interacting with any website. 

YOUR ACCOUNT AREA   
This area of the Site is for the benefit of Users. The private areas of the Site facilitate communication and the exchange and sharing of information between employers and job seekers. The information contained in private areas is not used for any purposes other than to facilitate communication and the exchange of information between the parties involved. Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs reserves the right to monitor communications in the private areas in order to verify compliance with our Terms of Service, international, federal or state laws and/or our other stated policies. 

INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT   
Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

Web Server Logs.   
When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

Your Internet protocol address.  
The kind of browser or computer you use.  
Number of links you click within the site.  
State or country from which you accessed the site.  
Date and time of your visit.  
Name of your Internet service provider.  
Web page you linked to our site from.  
Pages you viewed on the site.

Use of Cookies   
Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs a site that relies on third-party cookies).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

Personal Information Users   
Visitors to our website can register to use services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

To fulfill your service requests for services.  
To protect ourselves from liability,  
To respond to legal process or comply with law, or  
In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

Public Information   
As part of registration, you may set up a Profile describing your experience and qualifications. After becoming a member, in order to apply for some jobs, you must create a Profile, and in order to create a Profile, you will be required to provide some information about your background (such as your resume). If you decide to apply for a job, potential employers may review your Profile to help them decide whether to contact you for an interview. Your resume BECOMES PUBLIC and opened to the Internet. Therefore we advise that you DO NOT POST YOUR PERSONAL CONTACT INFORMATION IN YOUR PUBLIC RESUME IF YOU DO NOT WANT YOUR INFORMATION TO BE PUBLIC ON THE INTERNET. Information in your Profile is available for any other registered User to access. We will not have any   
obligation under this Privacy Policy with respect to information in your Profile or information you voluntarily provide to other Users via the Site. We are not responsible for the information that you make public via your profile and resume. All content provided by you is your own responsibility. Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs is not liable for any actions or instances as the result of the information you post in our public website areas.

CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT   
Virtual Office Temps/Virtual Assistant Jobs has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the updated date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

CONTACTING US   
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please send your comments to: info@virtualassistantjobs.com 

|  |  |  | 

* * *

Featured Virtual Assistants

| Sr Online Corporate expert  
---  
Marketing Communications and Event Managment...  
Virtual Virtual Assistant  
Administration  
Virtual Consultant and Assistant  
Nicole  
Virtual Assistant with Accounting, Web...  
Management Experience  
Virtual Assistant , Data Entry, Cl  
Working as a vovation, not as a profession  
  
* * *

Jobs & Projects At A Glance

Follow Up Assistants  
---  
Clerical / Customer Assistants  
Virtual Research Scanners  
Virtual Marketing Specialists  
Customer Account Representative and Processor  
Real Estate Monitors and Recorders  
Virtual Assistants  
Virtual Admin Assistants  
Podcast Transcribers  
Data Entry, Customer Service, Admin  
Customer Consumer Service Assistants   
Data Typing Agents  
Legal Typists and Transcribers  
Data Typists and Transcribers  
Legal Typing  
Audio Typists  
Email Data Assistants  
Data Entry and Research  
Remote Live Office Agents  
Virtual Phone Agents  
Live Remote Receptionists  
VIRTUAL Admin Financial Services  
VIRTUAL Keyers  
VIRTUAL Financial Data Keyers  
Medical and Legal Typist Transcribers  
Human Resources Customer Service Agent  
Virtual Medical Transcriptionists Needed  
Seasonal Keyers Needed NOW  
Executive Administrative Research Associates  
Web Data Assistants  
Virtual Coders  
Virtual At Home Agents  
At Home Virtual Telephone Reps  
At Home Team Members  
Department Store Virtual Customer Service  
Typing Transcriptionists  
Data Entry Coding Assistants  
Administrative Data Recording  
Online Social Media Assistants  
Text Chat Agents  
Search All...  
  
* * *

Keep Up With the VOT Blog

Resumes For Virtual Administrative Secretarial Jobs  
---  
Establishing Your Virtual Identity  
Become a Guest Writer For VOT  
Home Based Social Networking Jobs Fastest Growing New Virtual Field  
Freelance Your Way to a Virtual Assistant Job  
Virtual Jobs With Top Fortune 500 Employers  
Best Virtual Work At Home Jobs for 2012  
10 Real Work At Home Jobs You Can Get Now  
Real Virtual Data Entry Jobs  
Setting Up Your Virtual Assistant Website  
Become A Medical Transcriptionist and Get Hired Now  
Virtual Assistants Free Career Certifications Coming Soon  
Celebrating Administrative Professionals Day  
Create A Job Winning Virtual Assistant Resume and Website  
How Virtual Assistants Can Use Pinterest To Work From Home  
View All...
